{
    "subject": "resource/Gina_Torres",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/New_York_City",
    "human_readable": "Gina Torres was born in New York City.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9590033888816833,
            "question": "Is Gina Torres from New York City?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9308723211288452,
            "question": "Where was Gina Torres born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8844192028045654,
            "question": "Gina Torres's birthplace is in which state?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.84267657995224,
            "question": "What city is associated with Gina Torres's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6418539881706238,
            "question": "If Gina Torres were to return to her birthplace, what might she experience?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5142900943756104,
            "question": "In what US city did Gina Torres come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3424409031867981,
            "question": "What is known about Gina Torres's early life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3004913628101349,
            "question": "Do you know any other famous people who were born in New York City?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18697692453861237,
            "question": "Could Gina Torres's upbringing have influenced her career choices?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.050844062119722366,
            "question": "What are some popular cultural attractions in New York City?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Gina Torres was born in New York City.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7058_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could Gina Torres's upbringing have influenced her career choices?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7058_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know any other famous people who were born in New York City?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7058_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about Gina Torres's early life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7058_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7058_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7058_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7058_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7058_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7058_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7058_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7058_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7058_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7058_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7058_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Gina Torres was born in Manhattan, New York City, which supports the statement that she was born in New York City."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}